

### **PROFILE**

Automation Test Engineer with 9+ years of experience. Developed and enhanced automation frameworks and scripts for cloud-based enterprise Web, Desktop, API applications using tools like Selenium, CodeceptJS, TestStack White, CodedUI, JMeter, Rest Assured with languages Python, Java, C# dotnet, JavaScript.

### **AUTOMATION TOOLS**

- Selenium WebDriver
- Rest Assured
- CodeceptJS
- Test Stack White
- Coded UI
- Appium
- JMeter

#### **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES**

- Python
- C# dotnet
- Java
- JavaScript

### **OTHER TOOLS**

AWS, Jenkins, JIRA, TestRail, GIT, NUnit, Junit, TestNG, SQL, Postman, Octopus Deploy, PyTest, Gherkin, Cucumber, Browser Stack, Lambda Test, Bitbucket, Linux, Windows, MacOS, Swagger

### **EDUCATION**

## Narsee Monjee Institute of Management Studies (NMIMS)

A Grade, Feb 2017 to May 2019 Executive MBA, Finance and Operations

# Sreenidhi Institute of Science and Technology (SNIST, JNTU University)

A Grade, 76%, June 2008 to May 2012 Bachelor of Technology, Electronics and Computer Engineering (ECM)

### **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Hindi
- Telugu

# ABHILASH SANNE ISTORY

PHONE: +91 9912085300 LINKEDIN: <a href="www.linkedin.com/in/sanneabhilash/">www.linkedin.com/in/sanneabhilash/</a>
EMAIL: <a href="mailto:sanneabhilash">sanneabhilash</a>
GITHUB: <a href="mailto:sanneabhilash">sanneabhilash</a>

Hyderabad, India Hacker Rank: <a href="https://hackerrank.com/sanneabhilash">hackerrank.com/sanneabhilash</a>

#### **KEY ROLES PLAYED**

- Built Hybrid UI and API integrated Automation Frameworks
- Reduced test execution time with custom execution strategies
- Built API based load test suite using JMeter
- Integrated AWS S3, Secrets Manager for test data and config management
- CICD integration with customized Jenkins Jobs for automation tests
- Collaborated with CTO for implementing test automation from scratch
- Integrated custom HTML and Video logs for test reports
- 3<sup>rd</sup> party tools and APIs integration for test automation frameworks
- Perform POCs to check automation compatibility with product

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Senior Software Engineer in Test, Zenoti, Hyderabad Dec2020-Present Part of Test Automation COE team, responsible for maintaining and developing test automation solutions across the organization. Maintained and Enhanced existing in-house JSON based code less automation tools using Python and dotnet based solutions to support API, Web, Mobile and Database Automation testing. Secured test configuration management by integration framework config management with AWS Secrets Manager. Integrated customized Extent reports for test results reporting. Developed support for test execution rerun for nightly runs.

**Principal QA Automation Engineer, Innominds, Hyderabad** Apr 2018-Dec 2020 Worked with start up projects as client for providing QA functional and automation testing solutions. Built and managed API regression automation suites with 99%+ execution efficiency. Streamlined Automation backlog and defect management in sprints. CICD Jenkins jobs integrations. Build JMeter load test automation suite. Implemented dynamic test data creation and clean up strategies.

Senior Test Automation Engineer, CDK Global, Hyderabad Jul 2015-Apr 2018 Build test automation framework and for API and Desktop based product testing using C# dotnet and Test Stack White. Migrated HP UFT based test scripts to C# dotnet automation framework. Built custom Jenkins jobs to support CICD integration along with JIRA integration and dynamic results reporting. Executed Regression, Smoke suites, analyzed failures and reported results to stake holders.

Test Automation Engineer, Infosys Ltd, Hyderabad

Develop C# CodedUI based test automation scripts. Execution of regression suite and analyzing failures. Performing Automation feasibility analysis on functional tests. Automation tests backlog creation. Migration of CodedUI Test Automation scripts and framework to Selenium Webdriver. Coordinating with cross teams understand functional scope, RCA and defect resolution.